http://www.shareplanner.com/component/content/article/2-uncategorised/24687-privacy-policy.html?Itemid=200742

Username or
Password ?
New Here?
Our website address is: https://www.shareplanner.com
SharePlanner, Inc.
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information, IP addresses or other details to help you with your experience. We also retain your information to be able to give you access to our content, products, and services. Some plugins we use on this website will also collect data for the benefit of our visitors.
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
• To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.• To improve our website in order to better serve you.• To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.• To quickly process your transactions.• To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products• To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
When you submit through our contact form we use that information for customer service purposes only and do not use it for marketing.
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for one day, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember Me", your login will persist for one week. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
We use cookies to:• Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.• Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.• Keep track of advertisements.• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.
If users disable cookies in their browser:If you turn cookies off it will turn off some of the features of the site.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
Google
Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en
We have implemented the following:• Remarketing with Google Analytics• Demographics and Interests ReportingWe, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.
Opting out:Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.
Facebook
We use Facebook to analyze what interests users the most so we can offer content best suited for them. We use Facebook advertising and remarketing. You can turn this off by disabling your cookies. Here is Facebook's data policy https://www.facebook.com/full_data_use_policy
Seva
We use Seva to analyze where users come from and what interests them the most to optimize their experience. Here is Seva privacy policy https://convertkit.com/privacy/
Who we share your data with
We do not trade or sell your personal data. Here is a list of third part providers we use to help operate this website:
PayPal: For transactions
Stripe: For transactions
Google and Facebook: For ads and analytics
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. We use Cloudfare to protect this website from any suspicious behaviour.
Your contact information
For any privacy concerns please contact us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
How we protect your data
Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.
We use regular Malware Scanning.
Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.
What data breach procedures we have in place
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:
We will notify you via email• Within 7 business daysWe will notify the users via in-site notification• Within 7 business days
What third parties we receive data from
We receive data about users from Facebook and Google. We also use ad networks.
What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data
We use Facebook custom audiences to optimize our ads to better serve our users with content and products most suited for them.
CAN SPAM Act
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.
We collect your email address in order to:
• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions• Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.• Send you additional information related to your product and/or service• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:
• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.
tweet
HOMEACADEMYTHE TRADING BLOCKSubscribePast PerformanceBLOGSwing-Trading Watch-ListDaily Swing-Trading StrategyCharts + Technical AnalysisTrading PsychologyTrading ToolsStrategies for TradingTechnical AnalysisTrading VideosSwing-Trading PodcastEpisodeABOUTSearchContact MeMerch
